{
    "id": "f8b686f8e4cf4cab99bf543f5934f767",
    "title": "Kinds Of Adjectives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Tokyo is a big city. Here big is an ………………….",
            "description": "Adjectives of quality show the kind or quality of a person or thing.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1462070ed09542d69d3af0d722ca155e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ate some rice. Here some is an ……………………….",
            "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e7cf34b7ca8439ba38f412b186b05f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The foolish crow opened his mouth to sing. Here foolish is an …………………………",
            "description": "Adjectives of quality show the kind or quality of a person or thing.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c64ee3b29acf4eb68eeb66b68548402f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has little patience. Here little is an ……………………………….",
            "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c8c552f46ae41b5af2ea2a12e9a019d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has lost all of his wealth. Here all is an ………………………….",
            "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "55c5246a9fbf4ccabcef5735859d493d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We did not receive sufficient rain this year. Here sufficient is an",
            "description": "Adjectives of quantity say how much of a thing is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bf244737ed4948488f17378cea1760fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each hand has five fingers. Here five is an …………………………",
            "description": "Adjectives of number show how many persons or things are meant.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ec91fc17d57b461c8a6cd79786ccb880"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are several mistakes in your composition. Here several is an ……………………….",
            "description": "Adjectives of number show how many persons or things are meant.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d1e4b695f5e740618db76d1a66b015c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "January is the first month of the year. Here the adjective first is an ……………………….",
            "description": "Ordinal numbers are all adjectives of number. ",
            "answers": [
                "adjective of quality",
                "adjective of quantity",
                "adjective of number"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa770842fa224dce86930b20694cce80"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our country expects every citizen to do their duty. Here every is a ……………………………",
            "description": "Distributive adjectives refer to each one of a group.",
            "answers": [
                "numeral adjective",
                "distributive adjective",
                "demonstrative adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5515130b2d8a433b86e0b75e507e07ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither accusation is true. Here neither is a …………………………..",
            "description": "Distributive adjectives refer to each one of a group.",
            "answers": [
                "numeral adjective",
                "distributive adjective",
                "demonstrative adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bcfc01ae9c74bb89117cc99cc461765"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those apples are ripe. Here those is a ……………………………..",
            "description": "Demonstrative adjectives point out which person or thing is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "numeral adjective",
                "distributive adjective",
                "demonstrative adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f5698a1d6c634301b18d526996ddcdea"
        }
    ]
}